[music]
Hello once again you are very
welcome to our YouTube channel today's
speed macaroni comparison between two half
insurance which is Liver and
Pressure Plan and HDFC Ergo Festival
Register of Clans and Joining 500
grams is the best of these two I am
your health and life insurance consultant
Kajal I keep giving you health and life insurance
so please through this channel
and give you advice on every problem related to insurance
I would
like to request all of you please
subscribe to my channel
please like my videos now press the button so that
you keep getting the latest updates regarding my videos let's start
today's video first of all we
will talk about the options so Rishal I will tell
you this
committee and options are available from three lakhs to one crore and Tiwari from
3 lakhs to 50 lakhs review this opens let's
know about the minimum maximum entries of this plan and both the province and
tourist plan  If we talk about constipation in the entry in the hanging minimum entry, then
I have given a maximum of
32nd
that
you can renew your policy with it
and if we
talk about the limit of both of these then I will not charge you any fee
and
I will give you
300 pages on
Friday. Now let's talk about the features
that you will get covered in two new policies. Let's
know about the benefits in infection treatment treatment plant.
You get 10,000 rupees, you can share and subscribe from the first day itself.
Subscribe
from 1520 to 5000 rupees.
From Magh to 100 rupees,
you get fifty percent of the
volume. The maximum volume goes up to hundred percent, that is, it is
doubled in front of you.
If you have two points in the quality phase,
which is reduced, that is,
50 percent only on our top and
in Parmeshwar Lal, you are given fifty percent as a no claim bonus in the
first year and fifty percent in the
second year, that is, hundred percent in 2 years,
which is reduced.  That Panipat
50% remained on, the
police took the body
into custody
and can hire any person
and subscribe for this tempered glass,
his treatment
cost was incurred and immediately after that
other members of his family also get it, then
for them also ₹10 more money has to be paid for the third and
fourth member also, so we will
also spend ₹10 in a frustrated mind, so
similarly you can take that special campaign of office unlimited registration
and you
can avail the benefit of registration only once a year in Tiwari Store and if you have
not subscribed to this then please like and
subscribe,
friends,
we will talk in this front,
in these matters, it
means you are crushed by it, you will
not have to pay in Duggi class
and there is no sub-limit here
because friends, this
is a huge advantage in itself, now we will talk about
some properties which are available to you not only in
your Chhapra, but also in Greater
Kailash, regarding if you want it above then
that too in the policy period  You
can take the plant in a year, it gives you a critical
advantage, it changes the quarter, so now the
most important thing is that
if
you use it, then for
whatever you
subscribe, the company gets
another benefit, in which there is
no interest on two benefits,
if you set up a claim policy up
to Rs 50,000 immediately, in
which there will be an increase according to the consumer price index,
subscribe for more than one year
and for pre-existing,
definitely like and subscribe, those who are 40 years old, then they have
taken 10 lakh 22 thousand 350 cups of sugar,
take 28 thousand 506 backup in 10 lakh or, now let's reduce another example sentence, so
we have taken the example and about the
powder, we did
10 lakh 29 thousand 285
dumbbells last year, so
about like and subscribe, then
I will call 50 thousand ten lakh 64 thousand 370 right now  If we reduce these plans by example, then
in the example we have a
mixture of 10 lakhs and what is 2 years coming
soon, but this person is 31
years old, now let us know about those people,
in Shivlal this is 10 lakh 16256 of 10 lakh 92 thousand 572,
so friends, the most important thing in health insurance policy is that
nowadays the new
plans are launched in which you
get more coverage,
you have to keep in mind that your posted
by, whenever you take an online policy or a banned
policy, you are not updated with all these things
because it may be that
your policy is old or it may be that a lot of changes
that were made in the policy have to be done in it, so
you should
take advice from someone to update your policy and let me
tell you that if you have taken a policy
holder, then now you can call us and
find out how you will get more benefits for
this policy, A A Fancy Ladies, a little
information about Short Plan and
Optima  To know more details about the comparison of Restore Plant, you
can contact us
and with the help of the number shown on them you
can get rid of it. So friends, that's all in today's
video, I hope
you found the rest of the information in this video useful.
We will keep bringing important information about Yogi Life and Health Insurance for you all.
Now we
want to thank you from the bottom of our hearts.
Because of your continuous contribution, today
our channel has a family of more than 14 thousand people. All the
people who are
connected with us, because you want to
stay with us in this journey and if you like the new version
then please subscribe to our channel
and be a part of our team.
In this video with me, you have liked it
very well
[Music]